https://www.360visibility.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - 360 Visibility
Call us if you have any questions:905-907-3600Customer Care365 CSP LoginCustomersCustomer StoriesIndustriesWholesale DistributionFinancial ServicesProfessional ServicesHospitalityNot-for-ProfitProperty ManagementAll IndustriesWhat We OfferMicrosoft DynamicsDynamics 365 Business CentralJet Reports for Business CentralDynamics 365 Sales & CRMDynamics GP to Dynamics 365 MigrationDynamics NAV to Dynamics 365 UpgradeBusiness Central Apps360 Canadian EFT360 Quick Sign360 Quick Link360 Smart Search360 Smart PricingProductivityMicrosoft Azure CloudMicrosoft Office 365Microsoft SharePointMicrosoft TeamsOffice 365 Email SignaturesProfessional Services Automation SoftwareServicesBusiness Impact AssessmentManaged Cloud ServicesManaged Cloud SecurityBusiness Central QuickStartUpgrade to Business CentralMigrate to Dynamics 365 Business CentralMove to Cloud AccountingSelf-Service Microsoft CSP LicensingDirect CSP Billing & Provisioning Platform for PartnersBlogCompanyOur StoryPartnersCareersContact Us
Home » Privacy PolicyPrivacy StatementWe Are Commited To Protecting Your PrivacyFor each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor’s internet (“IP”) address (where possible). If you should request additional information on this web site, or submit your information in response to a survey of other informational request, the information you provide us may be maintained by us for use in accordance with the purpose for which it was submitted. Such use may include providing you other information or marketing materials on related matters.The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes. The information is not shared with or sold to other organizations or 3rd party ad services for commercial purposes.With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, and customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type (or other information that the visitor sends).If you do not want to receive e-mail or direct mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email to opt-out@360visibility.com or by calling us at (905) 907-3600. We will be sure your name is removed from our email mailing list.If you supply us with your mailing address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us an email to opt-out@360visibility.com or by calling us at (905) 907-3600. We will be sure your name is removed from our mailing list.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us an email at opt-out@360visibility.com or by calling us at (905) 907-3600. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from our list.If our practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes within an updated privacy statement to notify you of these changes, and provide you with the ability to opt out. Upon request we provide site visitors the information that we maintain about them. Contact info@360visibility.com to request this information. If you find that we are maintaining incorrect information about you, we will make appropriate corrections.DisclaimerThe information on this website is compiled and made available as a public service by 360 Visibility Inc. However, 360 Visibility Inc. makes no warranty as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of the information and are not responsible for any errors or omissions or for results obtained from the use of the information. Distribution of the information does not constitute such a warranty. Use of the information is the sole responsibility of the user.We are a leading Microsoft Dynamics partner serving businesses in Toronto, Ontario, Canada and the United States. We specialize in Microsoft Dynamics 365 Business Central, Dynamics GP, Dynamics NAV, Office 365, and Microsoft Cloud.As a full-service Microsoft Tier 1 CSP Partner, we provide your business with 360° insight and solutions so you can See Clearly and Act Faster.Work with 360 Visibility Industries We HelpWholesale DistributionFinancial ServicesProfessional ServicesHospitalityNot-for-ProfitProperty Management The Perfect CloudMicrosoft Dynamics GPMicrosoft Dynamics NAVMicrosoft Dynamics 365 Business CentralMicrosoft Dynamics 365 Sales & CRMMicrosoft Azure CloudMicrosoft Office 365Office 365 Email Signatures Quick LinksSupportDocumentationPay OnlineCustomer Portal LoginCareersArchives Contact Us Send us an email 905 907 3600 Fax? Really? It's 2020. Who uses fax anymore?
Get the 360 View Newsletter Copyright © 2020 360 Visibility Inc.Privacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsCustomer Care365 CSP Login
